{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214846039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214846038"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtini_vyangu-ziwa-mumbi-mtini"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mtini"," userResponse":" mtini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214875835","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214875835"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njia_bado-njia-mbali-mbaya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" njia"," userResponse":" njia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214897288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214897288"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku_kila-nyumbani-kutoka-siku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" siku"," userResponse":" nyumbani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214901273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214901273"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku_kila-nyumbani-kutoka-siku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" siku"," userResponse":" kila"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214905217","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214905217"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku_kila-nyumbani-kutoka-siku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" siku"," userResponse":" kutoka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214907885","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214907885"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" siku_kila-nyumbani-kutoka-siku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" siku"," userResponse":" siku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214930058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214930058"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njia_njia-ule-hapa-ah"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" njia"," userResponse":" njia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214950415","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214950415"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka_bi-mwalimu-Nyoka-nyasi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Nyoka"," userResponse":" Nyoka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214972363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214972363"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziwa_uchungu-kujua-ziwa-binadamu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ziwa"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214985959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214985958"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ziwa_uchungu-kujua-ziwa-binadamu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214986099","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214986099"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" bd7c36d8-3b4b-4761-a5eb-12a648a48977"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha ____________!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214995704","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214995704"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214996558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214996557"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214997580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214997580"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214997824","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214997824"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214998378","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214998378"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214998942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214998942"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214999118","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214999117"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549214999192","data":{"timestamp":" 1549214999192"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.21__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215008102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215008102"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215014565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215014564"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215022094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215022094"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 9e822717-6586-4b10-8e3b-76a7a3566742"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215032662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215032662"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215033395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215033395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215033828","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215033828"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215036620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215036620"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215036823","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215036823"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215037816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215037816"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215038139","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215038139"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215041158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215041158"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215041381","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215041381"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215042084","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215042084"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215042997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215042997"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215045059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215045059"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215045541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215045541"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215046254","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215046254"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMA"," userResponse":" MWEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215046858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215046858"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215047362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215047362"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215048315","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215048315"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRA"," userResponse":" SUBIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215051903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215051902"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOSUKA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOSUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215052365","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215052365"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215053079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215053078"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215054641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215054641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ZINAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215055184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215055184"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215059147","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215059147"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" AMEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215059451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215059450"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215060173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215060173"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215060456","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215060456"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215061528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215061527"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGIRANGI"," userResponse":" RANGIRANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215064484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215064484"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215065247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215065247"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215065548","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215065548"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215065754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215065754"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215066346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215066346"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215066590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215066590"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215067534","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215067534"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215068956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215068956"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215070317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215070315"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215070971","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215070970"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215071844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215071843"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215074844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215074843"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215076302","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215076301"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215077249","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215077249"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISUKIE"," userResponse":" NISUKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215077642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215077642"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215078310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215078309"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215078823","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215078822"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWE"," userResponse":" ZIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215079358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215079358"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215079584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215079583"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215080363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215080362"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215080807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215080806"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215084354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215084353"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEKUWA"," userResponse":" NINGEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215084662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215084661"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215085317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215085316"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215086274","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215086274"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215088044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215088044"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" NINGEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215088621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215088621"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215089269","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215089269"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215089492","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215089491"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215090149","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215090148"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215093879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215093878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUA"," userResponse":" NITAKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215094453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215094453"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215095566","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215095566"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215096163","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215096163"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215096913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215096912"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215097359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215097358"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215100127","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215100126"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215100237","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215100237"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215108950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215108950"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215119219","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215119219"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215125998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215125998"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215132722","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215132722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215139891","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215139891"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 0be78095-ba60-47f7-8a77-8dc5b31b90fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215150901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215150901"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215151404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215151404"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215152109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215152108"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215153262","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215153262"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" ANALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215156569","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215156568"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215157542","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215157542"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215158104","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215158104"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215160601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215160601"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215161124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215161124"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215161896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215161896"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215163270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215163270"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215166501","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215166501"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215167694","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215167694"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215168196","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215168196"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215168869","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215168869"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215171442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215171442"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215171895","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215171895"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215172698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215172698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215174421","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215174421"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215176912","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215176911"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215177654","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215177654"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215178197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215178197"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215179000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215179000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215179952","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215179952"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" JIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215182496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215182495"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215182978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215182978"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215183611","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215183611"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215185074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215185074"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" ANACHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215187761","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215187761"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215188474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215188474"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215189746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215189746"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" AMESOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215191049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215191049"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" KICHEKESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215193554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215193554"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215194037","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215194036"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215194540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215194539"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215195033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215195033"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215196856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215196856"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" ANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215200280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215200280"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215200793","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215200793"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215201927","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215201927"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" WANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215202740","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215202739"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215203692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215203692"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215204813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215204813"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215204864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215204864"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215211437","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215211437"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" d0b86f68-3c9a-4960-945a-0ba411749626"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215221565","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215221565"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 8362528f-d1ce-4002-80ca-4d7cfb99bfbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-7-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215226632","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215226632"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 8362528f-d1ce-4002-80ca-4d7cfb99bfbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-7-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215231368","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215231368"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 8362528f-d1ce-4002-80ca-4d7cfb99bfbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_8-7-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215238399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215238399"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 8362528f-d1ce-4002-80ca-4d7cfb99bfbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-5-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215242851","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215242851"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 8362528f-d1ce-4002-80ca-4d7cfb99bfbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-5-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215247969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215247969"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 8362528f-d1ce-4002-80ca-4d7cfb99bfbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549215276017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549215276017"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_202644"," gameId":" 8362528f-d1ce-4002-80ca-4d7cfb99bfbc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}